<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GatdaWatda</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="goback">aa1</string>
    <string name="aaa">aa2</string>
    <string name="aaa1">aa3</string>

    <!-- Ted Permission -->
    <string name="permission_1">[설정] > [권한] 에서 권한을 허용할 수 있습니다.</string>
    <string name="permission_2">사진 및 파일을 저장하기 위하여 접근 권한이 필요합니다.</string>

    <!-- Sign In -->
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="signin_email">회원가입 및 이메일 로그인</string>
    <string name="signin_google">Google으로 로그인</string>
    <string name="signin_facebook">Facebook으로 로그인</string>
    <string name="signin_twitter">Twitter으로 로그인</string>
    <string name="signup_complete">회원가입 성공</string>
    <string name="signin_complete">로그인 성공</string>
    <string name="signout">로그아웃</string>
    <string name="signout_success">로그아웃 성공</string>
    <string name="signout_fail">로그아웃 실패</string>
    <string name="signout_fail_null">이메일과 비밀번호를 입력해주세요</string>
    <string name="title_activity_record2">activity_record2</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="sort_by_popularity">인기순</string>
    <string name="sort_by_latest">최신순</string>


    <string-array name="sort_by">
        <item>@string/sort_by_latest</item>
        <item>@string/sort_by_popularity</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>